<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manutastic</title>
    <description>Manu is a developer with a strong eye for design. He writes silly things here sometimes.
</description>
    <link>http://manutastic.com/blog/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://manutastic.com/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 03:37:49 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 03:37:49 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Automatically test your database backups.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the issues of yesterday’s GitLab.com “database incident” is that most of their database backups weren’t being tested, and when they needed a restore, they discovered that most of the backup methods hadn’t been working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Untested backup methods that turn out to be missing or broken are extremely common. I can’t fault them much because it’s a very easy mistake to make: most backups, by nature, never need to be restored from, so you never realize if something changes and they stop working… until it’s too late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solution is to frequently and automatically test backups by:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 23:45:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://manutastic.com/blog/jekyll/2017/05/09/automatically-test-your-database-backups.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://manutastic.com/blog/jekyll/2017/05/09/automatically-test-your-database-backups.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The future of computing.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The quarterly results are in and Apple’s doing fine overall, but the iPad really isn’t, with another year-over-year decrease in sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple and commentators can keep saying the iPad is “the future of computing,” and it might still be. But we’re starting its seventh year in a few months, and sales peaked three years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What if the iPad isn’t the future of computing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What if, like so much in technology, it’s mostly just additive, rather than largely replacing PCs and Macs, and furthermore had a cooling-fad effect as initial enthusiasm wore off and customers came to this conclusion?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The moving-average unit sales graph would look something like this, right?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 22:45:33 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://manutastic.com/blog/test/2017/01/31/the-future-of-computing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://manutastic.com/blog/test/2017/01/31/the-future-of-computing.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>test</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
